（イナゴマスク）トーッ！
（怪人）うッ！
Inago Kick!
イナゴキック！
うわッ…　ぐあ～ッ
Inago Mask, at the ready!
イナゴマスク　参上
（薫）やったーッ　イナゴマスク！
Yay, it's Inago Mask!
わあ～ッ！
Go go, Inago Mask!
いけいけ　イナゴマスク！
Go go!
いけいけ～
Kaoru's really enjoying this.
〈（純一）薫のやつ　ノリノリだな〉
All right, Inago Mask!
さあ　イナゴマスク
一気に倒しちゃって
Get him in one hit!
Inago Punch!
イナゴーパンチ！
うわッ
キック！
ああ！
Kick!
Wait, no way...
うそッ　ちょっと…
Inago Attack!
イナゴ　アタ～ック！
うわ～ッ！
ああ…　薫のやつ
これ　台本にない展開じゃないか
Damn it, Kaoru...
This wasn't in the script!
I'll show you.
見てろよ
Thanks to all of you, Inago Mask has won!
みんなのおかげで
イナゴマスクが大勝利
Behind you, behind you!
（子供達）うしろ　うしろ～
えッ？
Super Change: Namako Man!
スーパーチェンジ　ナマコ男
うわ～ッ！　ちょっ…　ちょっと
H-Hey!
Ultra Change: Kujira Man!
ウルトラチェンジ　クジラ男！
Kujira Splash!
クジラスプラ～シュ！
おおッ！
Squid! Squid squid squid squid...
イカ～　カッカッカッカッ…
Deluxe Change: New Squid Man!
デラックスチェンジ　新イカ男
参上！
At the ready!
If you're wondering why we're doing this,
〈どうして私達がこんなことを
しているかというと〉
a certain plan came up between Junichi and me just before summer break.
〈夏休みに入るちょっと前に〉
〈私と純一の間で
ある計画が持ち上がったのです〉
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
う～ん
グッモー！
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
おはよう
こんな朝早くから呼び出して
何の相談？
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
実は…
美術の宿題？
なかなかうまく描けなくて
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
このままだと
まずいことになりそうなんだ
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
頼む　薫　手伝ってくれ！
Check My Soul
そういうことなら私に任せなさい
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
薫　絵が得意で本当によかったよ
どれどれ～
へえ　抽象画にしたの？
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
やけにハードル高いわね
いや…　これ
ここから見える風景なんだけど
え～ッ！　風景画なの！？
これが？
悪かったな
Good morn'!
ふ～ん　ちょっと失礼
うわッ
Morning.
What'd you call me out for so early in the morning?
何してんだ！？
えッ？　絵を直すのよ
Well...
なッ　何で　ここに座るんだよ
Art homework?
ダメなの？
ダメじゃないけど
I'm finding it hard to draw well...
だったら気にしない　気にしない
At this rate, I'll be in trouble.
そっちはいいかも
Please, Kaoru!
だけど…
Help me out!
う～ん
何とかなりそうか？
Sure, leave it to me.
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
どうするかなあ
Kaoru, I'm so glad you're good at drawing.
Let's see...
よし
Oh, so you're doing abstract art?
That's pretty difficult stuff.
Uh, it's supposed to be the scenery from here.
What? It's supposed to be landscape art?!
ああッ　うッ
Seriously?
あッ　あッ…
Sorry about that.
うわッ　うう…
Excuse me.
What are you doing?!
What? I'm fixing your work.
ははッ…
Wh-Why would you sit here?
ううッ！
I can't?
I-It's not that you can't...
あっは～
Then don't worry about it!
ああ…
You might be fine with it...
あッ？　たッ
But...
田中さん！？
Can you fix it?
（恵子）薫！
Let me think...
All right.
T-Tanaka-san?!
Kaoru!
Oh, Keiko.
ああ　恵子
What? Oh? Huh?
あれ？　えッ　うん？
はあ→
バカップルになってるよ
You guys seriously look like lovebirds.
えッ？
≪（恵子）だからさ
薫と橘君のことだよ
I'm talking about you and Tachibana-kun.
うん
（恵子）学校では　どうかな→
Right...
I dunno about doing it at school...
ほら　みんなの目があるでしょう？
I mean, won't everyone see it?
誤解よ　今朝のことなら
全然そういうんじゃないから
That's a misunderstanding!
What happened this morning totally wasn't what you guys thought.
（恵子）そうかもしれないけど→
Well yeah, but the two of you are technically dating now.
二人は　ほら
もうつきあっているわけだし
バカップルに見えた？
Did we look like lovebirds?
≪（恵子）うん
Yeah.
うわッ　恥ずかしい～！
I'm so embarrassed!
I know you guys are still really friendly with each other despite having dated for over half a year.
もう半年以上もつきあっていて
それでも前と変わらず
仲がいいっていうのも分かるよ
分かるけどさ…
I know, but...
The two of us...
私達二人は…
あんまり
変わってないつもりなんだけどな
...don't really want to change how things are, though.
≪（恵子）ああいうのは二人きりに
なったときじゃないとね
Either way, you guys should keep that sort of thing to when you're alone together.
Alone together, huh?
二人っきりかあ
Alone together...
二人っきり…
そういえば　私と純一
Now that you mention it, what do Junichi and I do when we're alone together?
二人っきりのときって
何してたんだろう？
Pretty much the same things you did before you started dating, right?
≪（恵子）それって　つきあう前と→
あまり
変わってないってことだよね？
うん
Yeah.
ねえねえ　薫
Hey, Kaoru.
もうすぐ夏休みだし
橘君と旅行するとかはどうかな？
It's almost summer break, so how about going on a trip with Tachibana-kun?
えッ　旅行？
A trip?
うん　な～んたって
高校生最後の夏休みなんだよ
Yeah.
It'll be your last summer break of high school, after all!
ねッ！？
Well?!
最後の夏休みか…
Our last summer break, huh?
うん
Yeah.
そうね！
You're right!
えッ　旅行？
Huh? A trip?!
Yeah, a trip.
うん　旅行
It'll be our last summer break of high school, after all.
高校生活最後の夏休みだもん
青春の１ページに
思い出を刻みたいじゃない？
Don't you want to mark the first page of our adolescence with a memory?
旅行か…
A trip, huh?
ねえ　純一は　どこに行きたい？
So where would you like to go?
う～ん　そうだなあ…
Let's see...
《純一》
Junichi!
Junichi...
《純一》
Junichi.
う～ん
純一！
Junichi!
僕は水着でも浴衣でも裸でも
何でも…
I'm fine with you wearing a swimsuit, a yukata or nothing at all...
はあ？　何言ってんの？
えッ
Huh? What are you talking about?
ああ　あっははは…
でも旅行だなんて
B-But a trip?
僕の懐には　そんな余裕は
これっぽっちもないぞ
I don't have any money in my wallet.
だからアルバイトしないとって
Then you'll have to pick up some part-time jobs.
旅行資金獲得のために
頑張って働くのよ
Work hard and get the money to go on the trip!
うん？
これこれ
Check this out!
Inago Mask Hero Show
Looking for Part-time Staff!
Won't you join forces with the heroes
to fight the battalions of evil?
ヒーローショーのスタッフ…
Staff for a hero show...
I've never had a part-time job
before, so I dunno if I can do it...
僕　アルバイトやったことないから
自信ないな
大丈夫　私に任せなさい！
Don't worry!
You can count on me!
イナゴマスクがピンチになったとき
When Inago Mask gets into a tough spot, you can help him by cheering for him!
それを助けられるのは
みんなの応援です
みんな　大きな声で「イナゴマスク
頑張れ！」って言ってくださいね
Everyone, be sure to yell,
"Inago Mask, hang in there", okay?
（子供達）はーい
Okay!
All right everyone, let's give it a try!
一度
みんなで練習してみましょう
One, two!
せーの　頑張れ！
Hang in there!
頑張れ～！
もう一度
Hang in there!
One more time!
頑張れ！
頑張れ～！
Hang in there!
そうそう　その調子
Yes, just like that!
じゃあ　みんな　頼んだわよ
それでは　いよいよ始まりま～す
All right, we're counting on you!
It's now time to start the show!
みんな最後まで楽しんでね
Please enjoy it until the very end!
All right.
よしッ
Squid! Squid squid squid squid...
イカーッ　カッカッ　カッカッ　カッカッ…
新イカ男様の力を
甘くみたんじゃなイカ？
You've underestimated the power of New Squid Man!
はあ？　そんなセリフ　台本に
Huh? This wasn't in the script!
Afghan of Anger!
怒りのアフガ～ン！
うわ～ッ！
わあ～　新イカ男　スゲエ！
Whoa, New Squid Man's awesome!
頑張れ　新イカ男！
Go for it, New Squid Man!
どうだ　参ったか　薫
Well? Do you give up, Kaoru?!
これが新イカ男様の本当の力…
This is the true power of New Squid Man...
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]（スタッフ）こら～ッ！　怪人と司会が
イナゴマスクより目立ってどうする！？
What's the point if the monster and MC stand out more than Inago Mask?!
≪（スタッフ）まったく　君達のせいで
ショーがメチャクチャだよ→
Damn it, you guys totally messed up the show.
バイト料　半分だからね
You're only getting half the pay.
あんなに頑張って　これだけとは
We only got this much after all that work...
スタッフの人　ずいぶん怒ってたもんな
The staff were pretty mad.
ホントは割がよくて
楽しい仕事のはずだったのよ
This was supposed to be a fun job with good pay.
もう二度と来るなって
言われちゃったしな
They even told us never to come again.
まったく…　純一が
台本にないことするからじゃない
Geez, it's all because you
decided to totally ignore the script.
それは薫もだろう？
You're as guilty of that as I am!
あら　そうだっけ？
そうだよ
Huh? I am?
You are!
あっはは
それに…
Plus...
薫がイナゴマスクの味方ばかりするから
何か
You kept taking Inago Mask's side...
悔しくて　つい
I didn't like that, so I...
それは仕方ないでしょう？
But I had to!
もう　しょうがないわね
Geez, you're so hopeless.
ふふ　あはは…
あ～あ　静かな山荘も
海辺のコテージも夢と消えたか
There goes my dreams of going to a
quiet mountain villa or a cottage by the sea.
何　言ってるのよ
またすぐにバイト探して
What are you talking about?
We'll find another job right away and do anything it takes to go to a trip this summer break!
何としてでも
夏休み中に旅行に行くわよ
はッ
薫？
Kaoru?
ふふ～ん
期間限定味　ゲット！
I got a limited-time flavor!
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
40% Fruit Juice
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
40% Fruit Juice
Summer Only
Watermelon                         Tomato Soda
It's good!
おいしい！　飲んでみる？
えッ？　いいよ
Wanna try?
I'm fine.
何言ってるのよ　私がすすめてるん
だから間違いないって
Oh, come on.
You know it'll be good since I recommended it!
O-Okay...
ああ…
It's good!
うまい！
でしょう？
I know, right?
ああ　ちょっと！
私の分も残してよね
W-Wait! You left some for me, right?
Hey, when will you stop drinking it?!
ああ　ちょっと
いつまで飲んでんのよ！？
Geez...
もうッ
Hey, there's none left...
何よ　もうないじゃない
えっへへへ　ごめん
Sorry.
もう～　しょうがないわね
Well, what can I do?
This was the last can.
これ最後の１本だったのよ
Sold
Out
Kibitou Tours
うん？
National and
International Tours
Super Cheap
Bus Tours!
どうした　薫？
What's the matter, Kaoru?
ああ？　うわッ
純一　見て！
Junichi, look!
バス旅行か
A bus tour?
Limited Offer
Summer Holiday Special Plan
Super Cheap!! Bus Tour
For the first ten pairs of customers!
この値段なら
明日にでもすぐ行ける！
It's so cheap, we can even go on it tomorrow!
ああ！
やったわね！
Yeah!
I'm so happy!
I'm so jealous of you, boss!
≪（梅原）うらやましいぜ　大将～→
俺の夏休みは
寿司修業一色だってのに
And I'm stuck with making sushi for the whole of summer break...
でも深夜バスの貧乏旅行だからな
It's a budget tour on a late-night bus, though.
何　言ってんだ愛があれば金なんて
えへ
What? Who needs money when you've got love?
So, boss, since I'll probably be playing with
fireworks all alone by the river this summer as well...
で大将　この夏も河原で
一人花火になりそうな俺のために
あれ
持ってきてくれたんだろうな？
Did you bring you-know-what ?
ああ
Yeah.
うん？
う～ッ　このお宝が俺の救世主だぜ
This porno will be my messiah!
この夏は俺は寿司修業
大将は男修業か
So this summer, I'll be on sushi training and you'll be on man training, huh?
頑張れよ！
Work hard at it!
なッ　何を頑張るんだよ！？
Bath and Steam
Work hard at what?!
そう　バス旅行
Yeah, a bus tour.
Three days and two nights.
２泊３日なのよ
What? You'll be spending nights?!
[TEL]（恵子）えッ　泊まりなの！？
Well, uh... It's true that I'm the one
who recommended going on a trip...
[TEL]それってそれって…　確かに
旅行をすすめたのは私だけど
[TEL]日帰りだと思ってた
But I was thinking of a one-day trip...
It says two nights, but we'll be sleeping on the bus.
２泊っていっても
車中で２泊だからね
[TEL]そうなんだ　びっくりした
I see... You scared me.
何　びっくりしてるのよ
恵子にも　お土産買って帰るね
Why would that scare you?
I'll buy you something on the trip.
[TEL]私に気を使わなくていいから
You don't have to worry about me.
[TEL]旅行中は　何ていうか　その…
Well uh, during the trip...
[TEL]頑張ってね
Work hard at it.
W-Work hard at what?!
なッ　何を頑張るのよ！？
Starting tomorrow...
いよいよ明日
純一と二人っきりか…
I'll be alone with Junichi, huh?
やだ　何考えてるの？　私
Oh no, what am I thinking about?
〈こうして私と純一は〉
And that's how Junichi and I
managed to go on our desired trip.
〈何とかかんとか念願の旅行が
できることになったんです〉
ふふん
何だよ　何かおかしいか？
What? Is something wrong?
えッ　そうじゃないけど
That's not it.
何かね
You know.
楽しみだな
そうね
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
ねえ　純一　バスまで競争よ
Hey, Junichi.
It's a race to the bus!
Hey! Wait, Kaoru!
ああ　待てよ　薫！
薫　そっちじゃないぞ！
Kaoru, that's not where it is!
What?
えッ？
うっそだよ～
Just kidding!
ああ　ずる～い
Meanie!
A race is a race.
勝負は勝負だ
罰ゲーム　何にしようかな
What should I make you do for your punishment?
うん　もう…
Geez...
Off we go.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]出発しま～す
じゃ～ん
おッ　買い込んだな
Tada!
You bought a lot.
限定味ばかり　集めてみました
I got all the limited-time flavors.
さっすが　薫
It's just like you to do that.
はい　あ～ん
Here, say "ahh".
ああ…　あッ
What the hell, Kaoru?
何だよ　薫
あははは
ざんね～ん
シーッ！
Too bad for you!
ねえ　純一
うん？
Hey, Junichi.
純一は　ここは絶対
行っておきたい所ってあるの？
Do you have anywhere you really want to go to on this trip?
えッ　僕は別に…
Not really...
何よ　つまんないわね
せっかくの旅行なのに
Don't be so boring.
We're on a trip and all.
そうじゃなくて　僕は…
うん？
That's not it.
I...
僕は　薫が行きたい所へ
行ければいいかなって…
I don't mind going anywhere if it's where you want to go...
えッ？
ああ…
ああ　そうだ
薫　さっきの罰ゲーム　やるぞ
Oh, I know.
Kaoru, it's time for your punishment.
You have to eat the chocolate part only.
チョコの部分だけを食べるべし
But you're not allowed to touch my lips.
ただし
僕の口に触れちゃダメだからな
Wh-Why do I have to do something so lame?
何よ　そんな　くだんないこと
できないのか？
やるわよ！
You can't do it?
I'll do it!
やればいいんでしょ
That's all I need to do, right?
ああッ
うう…
うん？
ああ…
あッ　ああ
ああ？
あッ　はあ…
うん　うッ…
うう　うッ
はッ…
ああ…
うッ　うう
（一同）ああ→
あッ！
うん？
うッ
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]それでは２０分休憩します
We'll be taking a 20-minute break.
う～ん
腰が痛い
My back hurts...
やっと休憩か
We finally get a break!
It's tough to just sit there for so long.
座りっぱなしは
やっぱりちょっとキツイな
格安旅行なんだからね
文句と贅沢は禁止よ
It's a budget tour, after all.
No complaining or being greedy!
はいはい
ていうか　僕としては
Okay, okay.
But to me, well... how do I say this...
何ていうか
薫と二人で旅行ができただけで
I'm just really glad that I can go on a trip alone with you, Kaoru.
よかったなって
思ってるんだけどな
もう何よ！　純一ったら
Geez, what's with you, Junichi?!
You say the nicest things!
うれしいこと
言ってくれるじゃない
イッテテテ
Ow...
Limited-time Flavors !!
薫　まだ買うのか？
Kaoru, you're gonna buy more?
Limited-time Flavors !!
お菓子
たくさん残ってるじゃないか
We still have a lot of snacks left.
だって
ここは限定味の宝庫なんだもの
But this is a treasure trove of limited-time flavors.
今まで食べたことない味を
試さないわけにはいかないでしょ
I can't possibly pass up the chance to try out flavors I've never had before!
そう…　そうなのか？
R-Really?
贅沢は
禁止だったんじゃないのか？
Didn't you say that we can't be greedy?
これは別　だって
ここでしか買えない限定品よ
This is different.
Sample
You can't buy this limited-time stuff anywhere else!
まさに一期一会じゃない
It's like a one-in-a-lifetime encounter!
贅沢じゃないわよ
It's not being greedy.
ふう…
あッ！
Kaoru, I know you said that it's a
treasure trove of limited-time stuff,
薫…　お前　いくら
限定品の宝庫だっていっても
限度ってものが
えへへ
but this is too much...
どうするんだ？
そんなに買い込んで
What are we gonna do with all this stuff?
みんなへのお土産よ
自分で食べるのもあるけど
They're for everyone back at home!
I'll be eating some of this myself, though.
いったん　これバスに置いてくるね
I'll go drop this off on the bus.
All right.
よし
う～ん
ちょっと恥ずかしいかな？
This is kinda embarrassing.
純一！
Junichi!
身軽になったわよっと
I've dropped off my load!
だからって
もう買わなくていいからな
Well then, just don't buy any more.
分かってるわよ
薫
I know!
Kaoru, won't the people on the bus laugh at you if
they see the mountain of snacks you're bringing back?
あんなに
お菓子の山を持って帰って
バスの人達に
笑われたんじゃないか？
大丈夫よ
完璧なカムフラージュをしましたので
Don't worry.
I did the perfect camouflage.
カムフラージュ？
ほら　そんなことより早く！
Camouflage?
Come on, we need to hurry!
あ～ッ　ちょっ…
Wait...!
Eel and Tea Set
Ahh, I really want to try this!
ああ　これこれ
これ　食べたい！
まだ食べるのかよ
だって　ここの名物メニューなのよ
You still want to eat?!
Japanese Eel and Tea
Restaurant
But this place is famous for this food!
食べないわけにはいかない
またそれか
I can't possibly pass up this chance!
That again?
でもそろそろ戻らなくちゃ
いけない時間じゃないのか？
But don't we have to go back to the bus soon?
えッ？　２０分まで休憩って
言ってなかったっけ？
Huh? Didn't they say we have until 20 past?
えッ　そうだっけ？
そうよ　余裕よ　余裕
Huh? They did?
Yeah! We have plenty of time!
Come on, we're losing precious time discussing this!
ほら　ごちゃごちゃ言ってる時間が
もったいないわよ
うん？　寝てるのかな？
Hmm? I guess they're sleeping.
（運転手）では
お客様全員揃ったようですので→
Well, it looks like everyone's here.
そろそろ出発します
We can get going.
（バスのドアが閉まる）
いやあ　おいしかったな～
Man, this was really good!
でしょ
食べてよかったでしょう？
See? Aren't you glad we had it?
Yeah, seriously.
ああ　本当に
あッ　時間だ
Ah, it's time.
そろそろ戻りましょうか？
そうだな
We should head back.
Yeah.
ああ？
ああ…
I'm pretty sure this was where the bus stopped.
確か　ここに止まってたはずだよな
うん
Yeah.
これじゃないよな？
色が違う
This isn't the bus, right?
No, the color's different.
これじゃないよな？
模様が違う
This isn't the bus, right?
No, it looks different.
これじゃないよな？
形が違う
This isn't the bus, right?
No, it's shaped differently.
Which means...
と　いうことは…
もしかして
Don't tell me...
あッ　置いてかれた～！？
The bus left us behind?!
薫　楽しくやってるかな？
I wonder if Kaoru's having fun.
今頃　どの辺りなんだろう？
Where could she be right now?
We're screwed!
参ったな～
どうしよう
Now what?
All our luggage is on the bus.
荷物はバスの中に置いたままよ
とにかく
旅行会社に連絡してみよう
We should try calling the travel agency.
うん
Yeah.
（呼び出し中）
もしもし！
Hello-
This is Kibitou Tours.
[TEL]（アナウンス）こちらは
輝日東ツアーでございます
[TEL]ただいまの時間は営業時間外…
You have called outside of our business hours...
くそッ！
Damn it!
そうだ！
I know!
Incoming call...
（電話のベル）
（美也）ああ…
（電話のベルが鳴り続ける）
かき氷は　もういらないよ～
I don't want any more shaved ice...
どうだった？
Well?
そう…
I see...
なあ　薫
うん？
Hey, Kaoru.
僕達　今
二人っきりなんじゃないかな？
Are we all alone right now?
Looks like it.
そうね
But...
でも…
Yes, the two of us were alone at
the time, just like he had said, but...
〈そう　確かに純一の言うとおり〉
〈そのとき私達は
二人っきりになれたのですが…〉
What are we going to do?!
どうすんのよ　これから～！
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
（恵子）恵子です！　って薫
旅はどうだったの？
I'm Keiko!
So Kaoru, how was the trip?
いや　それが…
（恵子）どんなことがあったのかな
Well, about that...
Did anything happen?
I really wanna know!
頼むから　あんまり
あおらないでくれないかな
Can you please not make such a big deal out of it?
More importantly, did you buy us something from the trip?
（美也）そんなことより　お土産は
買ってきてくれたんだよね？→
もしかして忘れちゃってる？
ごめん　いろいろあってさ
Don't tell me you forgot?
Sorry! A lot of things happened, and...
It's fine, I'll settle with just stories of your trip.
（恵子）いいよ　いいよ　二人の
お土産話が聞ければ
What? Stories don't make you full!
（美也）話じゃ　おなか膨れないよ～
食べ物前提か？
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Companion
You just wanted food the whole time?
Next episode: "Companion".
（美也）つまんないの
How boring.